I'm going to concentrate on getting back to you with questions.
What do you want to do this summer?
My favorite black color.
Are you an idol?
Yes, I do!
What is your beauty secret?
Ask me!
Make your predictions in the comments section!
What makes each of you go "kyung"?
Yes, and now that I've had a delicious pizza
I'm going to concentrate on answering the questions!
Where do you eat taiyaki first?
The head, because I'm fast.
What do you value most in a live performance? This.
What do you think?
Everything is important to me, singing and dancing.
Making no mistakes.
To deliver something to the audience.
It's really important.
But I think the most important thing is to have fun.
If you see someone who doesn't look like they're having fun
If you see someone who is not having fun, you can't have fun.
I have to enjoy myself the most to have fun.
I also want to enjoy myself.
I'm not very good at singing or dancing.
I'm not very good at singing or dancing, but I'm trying my best to express myself with my facial expressions.
You're cute just by being alive.
What's going on?
Yes. You're cute just by being alive?
Yes, yes.
What's going on?
I'm doing my best.
Skin care for rough skin.
I'm telling you, just use the mildest products you can find.
And keep it simple.
Keep it simple.
Please keep it simple!
Just lotion and milky lotion is fine.
If your skin is rough
If your skin is rough, it's not good to put extra oil on it.
It's not good to put on extra oil or anything like that.
So...
And the face wash has a nice lather.
And also...
I recommend using a milk type cleanser.
For eye makeup, use eye makeup remover.
Makeup remover for eyes
and use the milk type for your skin.
Have you been to Disney recently?
Go to a new place.
I like it.
I want to go.
Your room is clean.
Not really.
I put my things away.
My sister's not clean right now.
She gets mad at me.
What did you study in college?
Various.
Marketing
Thank you for watching
I like you in model mode people thank you
Thank you. When you get the chance to do Kohaku.
Do you want to do it? Of course I would.
I want to be in it.
Very much.
Shibuya, the super beaver
How was it, Shibuya?
I asked guitarist Yanagisawa to write a song.
Of course I did.
Mr. Shibuya, Mr. Booyan...
He was very kind.
His face was tiny.
Yes.
Mr. Yanagisawa, Mr. Yanagi, Mr. Yanagi, I asked you to write a song.
I strongly requested you. Please write one.
Next, abroad... Italy, Italy, France...
What I want to do this summer is barbecue. I want to bring all the members to a barbecue.
My family consists of my mom, dad, me and my sister. I've been attacked by swimmers while driving.
I never get sleepy when I'm driving.
I sing all the time.
What kind of fans are easy to find at a concert?
Fans are easy to spot when they're passing around a fan or something.
And red, red, red, red.
I want to see your makeup every day.
I can't take pictures right now, so I'll take pictures next time.
I've had a lot of people tell me they want to see makeup videos every day.
I didn't really do anything today.
It's just skin, skin, skin.
A little bit of foundation.
Highlight.
I think highlighting is important.
I highlight a lot.
What is your favorite brand of clothes?
I recently went to Zero.
I wear a lot of Zero.
You don't go camping anymore?
I'd like to, but...
I've been busier than last year, thank God.
Rehearsals.
TV shows...
I've been doing a lot of TV shows and stuff.
I've been doing a lot of TV shows.
The day before
The day before or the day after
I'll see you soon.
If you have a big job or something...
Not too much.
It's not too dangerous.
But I can't get hurt.
Hmm...
Hit-chan's favorite cartoon.
Or manga.
Tokyo Ghoul is my favorite.
My favorite mole
back
and
Don't tell anyone
I have a few moles that people can't see.
mmm
Hmmm...
She's beautiful.
Are you an idol or something?
Yes, I am.
Part of the logo for this tour looks like a mirror ball.
It looks like a mirror ball.
It's a mirror ball.
It looks like a mirror ball beauty.
Let's see...
How did you come up with Leo's name?
My dad and sister decided on it on their own, so I'm a little confused.
I'm looking for a new bracelet.
Do you know any cute brands?
Bracelet
I don't know...
What kind?
It's not used.
I wear this one.
I'd wear this one.
I've got a brand new high bra.
How far do you want to drive?
I'd like to drive all the way around Japan.
If you have a day off
Do you use perfume?
Yes, I use it.
I love shishi shishi. What is the punchline of this song?
I like the part that is quite mensch.
I feel like I can get into the song.
I don't grow on people, but a lot of them are very bad at it.
Also, I take a bath absolutely every day.
I get in the boat at night.
I think I pump pretty much every day.
What is the 100th photo on your album?
I like this song.
Let's look at the 100th from the top?
The 100th album from the top?
Now? Now? Or from the past? Now?
It's an iPad. Take the cell phone.
The iPad's worth about a million dollars.
That's a picture of you at the beauty parlor.
That's the one.
This was it.
I prefer to take pictures horizontally, rather than vertically.
Like horizontally, and a little bit higher up.
That's right.
I don't know.
I think it's prettier if you get a little closer.
What I want you to do when you get together with your father.
What? Get together as a group.
Take a picture of everybody, and then get together.
Everybody get together, and look at this.
What I want you to do.
Cue everyone first!
Top 3 favorite costumes of Tokichen
I love this tour's costumes so much!
Princess of Makuhari
The costume of Gyutto
And also Girls Land
Chitori pattern
The next hairstyle I want to try
High tone
I want to try a high tone.
I want to change my clothes... I think the food is too delicious.
She said she liked it with a red gun at a benefit event.
Why don't you go see Hito-chan with some goods on?
What do you mean?
I don't want to.
What's Hito-chan's skincare regimen lately?
Before, lotion and packs.
Pack, pack, pack!
Hito-chan is always with her fans.
What do you pay attention to when you talk to your fans?
Do you pay attention to anything when you talk with your fans?
I talk a lot.
Yes, I do.
I talk too much, so I try not to talk too much.
What is your favorite language? Japanese, I guess.
What did you buy recently?
Ask me.
I won't open it today. It's still my birthday.
Listen to this
HITO-CHANNEL
I made an adult purchase, HITO-chan.
Guess and predict in the comments section!
Have I ever told you?
Jajan!
I went shopping at Chanel!
I've made up my mind that I won't open it until my birthday.
I won't open it.
I won't.
Also, my dad bought a new car.
I'm looking forward to driving it.
The sound of food...
The sound of food and water.
He's shy.
I'm very shy, very shy, very shy.
I'm not shy with people I don't know.
But I do to people I know a little.
I can't really talk to people in large groups.
Each one of them makes me swoon.
I'll tell her I like her at a storytime or something.
I think it's cute when she says she likes you and then she gets embarrassed.
I think it's cute.
What's your dad like?
Is he really cool? Very kind?
Oh, my God!
He's back.
I said, "Oh, Hito-chan's home.
Yes, I did.
You looked so cute in profile when you came to Karame.
And when I was crying.
You're cute when you're crying, too.
Yes.
That's how I feel.
I love the way you sing.
I love your singing voice.
What lyrics do you aim for?
What's your goal?
Do you have someone you admire?
Like Kanako.
Like Momokuro-san's Kanako.
I think she's amazing.
What?
Julia said sadly... that she's never been in the same room with Hito-chan.
She said sadly.
If all the rooms this time are for two, I'll be in the same room with Julia every time.
Can you teach me how to do bangs like Hisho?
Let's take a picture next time.
Do you have that kind of freedom? Bangs.
They're a little split today.
I only do it properly when I'm wearing that outfit.
Hmmm...
Top 3 favorite onigiri (rice ball)
Tuna
Salmon
Salmon roe
Have you ever had a bone structure diagnosis or a personal color diagnosis?
No, I have not.
Tell me, what is my skeletal structure?
What is my personal color?
I have some kind of blood vessels.
What is it?
What do you mean, blood vessels?
Blood vessels?
They're blue or purple.
You're a Bourbé.
You're a Yevi, for sure.
But they're blue and blue and blue.
Blue and purple.
Which is it?
Hmm.
I want to be as pretty as you.
If you smell it...
Let's wash it.
And then we can do something else.
I'm a self-study guy, really.
I spend a lot of time in front of the mirror when I go home.
You guys sing so well. Is there anything you do on a daily basis?
What? Not going to the hairdresser?
I do voice training. I do voice training. I also sing in the car.
We sing songs other than our own, and we also imitate the way artists sing to improve our singing.
If you imitate the way they sing, you will become a better singer.
Sta-chan's measures against heat stroke
I drink water
I drink a lot of water
Take vitamins and drink water
Eat salt recharge
Always delicious tea mas
Which do you prefer, sea urchin or soba noodles?
That's the question.
I used to eat udon, but now I prefer soba.
What kind of cake?
A cake?
Tart.
Which celebrity made you happy and which one would you like to meet?
I was happy to see Super Bieber.
I listen to his music so much.
I'd like to meet him.
I've met a lot of them.
I'd like to meet him
I'd like to meet him.
I've seen you before, Mirei Kiritani.
But I've never had a chance to talk to her.
Are you on a diet?
I don't.
But basically I eat one or two meals a day.
I only eat one or two meals a day.
Is that a diet?
If that's what you call dieting.
I'm on a diet.
What size are your feet?
23.5 or 24.
How did you get started in idolizing?
I was a cashier.
What do you eat every morning?
Fruit or yogurt?
The first one.
You're not allowed to eat juice for 6 days?
I'm banned! I want to.
Go on, then.
Let's see...
MVTA is ESA...
Is it still fj? No, it's changed.
I don't remember what it is.
My four-year-old daughter.
She wants me to take a shit.
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
That's what I said.
Me too.
I want you to put your best pictures in the story.
Sometimes I'd like to put a great shot in a great video.
I'm sure you'd love it.
It's a long time to get up in the morning.
I can get up in no time.
This morning was bad.
I've never once been to the beach.
I think I'm the only one.
I mean, you stay at hotels and stuff, right?
I've overslept a few times.
I've never done that.
I wake up right away.
I only set the alarm once.
I'm sure I'll do it someday.
I'm going to do it someday.
What's this thing you're obsessed with?
Skin.
Skin is the most important thing.
I want an electric suitcase.
What's that?
An electric switch.
Is this one okay?
What is your favorite food in Fukuoka?
Lots of food.
Go on.
How many open-back clothes do you have?
Well, I have a lot.
I probably have about 10.
How do you keep your bangs in place?
Use a cape to hold them in place anyway.
And if you put the back of your bangs up against the back of your head, it'll keep them in place.
And it won't get crushed by sweat.
Why are you so cute and handsome?
I think it's because of my dad.
I have a little bit of his personality.
Me.
I'm here because of Hitotsuan.
What should I do? What's wrong?
I think it's a good thing.
You've been getting a lot of media attention lately.
What's the point of your obsession?
Saying your name a lot.
Hmm.
What's the secret to being both pretty and beautiful?
Hmmm...
I think it's probably a lot of makeup and stuff.
And I think that being pretty is something you can do with your personality and gestures, but beauty...
But beauty...
I don't know.
Please choose three numbers from 1 to 18.
Seven.
Seven. Seven. Three.
Seventeen.
How many times do you have to be reborn to become a man's brother?
How many times?
I don't know.
Maybe one day when the day of destiny comes.
How do you relieve stress?
Eat, drive a car.
Get in touch with nature.
Hitachan, I've been wanting one lately.
I love it!
I'd like to have a chance to perform with straight hair again
I'm thinking of doing it on tour.
A way of life other than HITO-chan
Pichan.
Do you like me?
If we try to get another animal other than Ryok...
What was that?
The one that flies.
What was it?
I want to write "Otter
I want to write about otters.
Hmmm...
My routine when I get home
I'm going to take a bath right away.
I guess.
Is this one thing you can't give up, Hito-chan?
I don't want my feet to get scratches.
I really don't want to get scars on my feet.
I want to keep my feet clean.
How can I keep my skin
Do you all think I have fair skin?
What? You think I'm white?
For the face, you just need to take care of your skin.
The skin looks whiter when it's more hydrated.
So I try to increase the amount of moisture in my skin.
I also apply a lot of body cream.
Skin
That's right.
You should moisturize your whole body.
Hito-chan, here's what I ate today.
Pizza.
I want to be friends with Hito-chan
With an "A".
Are we done?
The end?
That's all they sent me.
It seems that's all they sent me.
I'm sure there's more.
I'll take a look.
So, Hito-chan's question return and
birthday project of eating wizards
It was a project that just made me happy
How did everyone like it?
Great!
Um...
I'm turning 23.
Yes, it's true.
It's true.
It's like my 10th birthday as an idol.
I've never changed.
I want to make everyone happy.
I want to make people smile.
I've been doing this for 10 years.
I will not change that.
This year, too, I'd like to give everyone
As an idol
I hope we can continue to deliver various things
I hope to deliver various things to you this year as an idol.
KANEKI
I myself
I'm getting a lot of energy from everyone.
I don't want to be dependent on everyone.
I feel like I can't do without it.
I'm getting a lot of power from you.
I'm going to do my best so that I can send energy to everyone.
You've been an idol for 10 years?
That's amazing.
I've always loved it.
I've been able to do it because I love it.
I think it's because of all of you.
Take care of everyone.
I'm going to put my health first
I'm going to enjoy myself.
Please continue to support Hito-chan!
I will do my best! Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching!